ARCADE
BEFORE GERALD CHEN DISAPPEARED
The professor's theory
is fundamentally flawed.
I've discussed it in the report.
You nearly finished?
Right.
SPECIAL OFFER ON TOKENS, 404
Uh, I'll get it to you
before 10:00. See you.
I forgot my power cord.
I'll see you back at school.
Don't move.
Move and I kill you.
Knifing me from that angle?
My grandma could do better.
What do we need you for?
Never forget what could be behind you.
Keep up your training.
It was Ben's voice that exposed you.
-Try again next time.
-Try again?
Let me make my will first.
Why'd you make such a mess here?
You were gone
for three or four months straight.
Can't you reply to messages?
You still wear this?
Uh, no. I just haven't thrown it out.
You want it?
Mina…
you were careless before.
Whatever you're in,
you must have a way out.
Hear me?
Got it.
And…
happy birthday.
I don't celebrate my birthday.
Stop singing! It's embarrassing.
I can't sing, then make a wish.
I don't want to. It's all bull.
You are such a child.
Don't be such a downer.
Come on, make a wish.
Try, will you?
THE FIXERS
TIEN-BU-LA
Don't get in the car.
Hey, you're…
How did William die?
You should be careful.
You were so close to him.
Do you think that you'll be spared?
Why the interest in Zoe?
Anyone who's connected to Zoe
will end up like William.
You don't think
he took his own life, do you?
I don't know.
If you wanna stay alive,
you need to tell us everything.
All I know is Zoe left the company
because she found out
William was moving Yuan Tao's funds
to invest in Tolita behind her back
to commit fraud.
Was he the reason she died?
William panicked when he found out.
And it wasn't an act.
You know what happened to Zoe's husband.
Zoe died a week after
he took his own life.
If you believe that.
The day Hsu Ming-yi died,
he called William.
And then?
William seemed very nervous
when he picked up. He said,
"Where did you hear that?"
"They're not to be messed with."
But the call cut out before he'd finished.
There you go. He probably
knew something and was silenced.
Have you seen this person before?
No.
After Zoe's death,
did William do anything strange?
Hey. Think carefully, all right.
Is there anything else?
One time, I helped him
move some dirty cash flow.
Why was that strange?
Because he wanted me
to store the money in a sound wallet.
That's not how we handle cash flow.
Sound wallet.
Any idea who it was for?
I don't know. He told me not to ask.
That's really all I know.
When you get to the airport,
don't make any calls.
Buy the earliest ticket out of here.
You hear me?
Could the person
William said shouldn't be messed with
and the person the sound wallet was for
be the same person?
Hey, what's this sound wallet doodad?
Crypto users have a 256-bit private key.
Each one has a recovery phrase.
You write it down, you could lose it.
But storing it on a computer
makes it easy to steal.
You can convert the recovery phrase
into an audio file.
You can access the account
by decoding the audio.
We could trace the money
and find further clues.
As long as we can decode the audio.
Seek and ye shall find.
But don't always trust what you hear.
Now William's dead.
We also don't know
where the sound wallet went.
Why do rich people
have to make things so complicated?
Having to use this damn wallet.
Seeing your money is so much simpler.
Isn't it?
Mina.
You said Gerald gave you your necklace?
Why are you looking into this audio file?
It's best you don't know.
Oh, here we go.
You said you'd buy me a meal
last time. You didn't.
Hey, Taro! Don't go there. I told you.
-You'll just hit someone.
-La, la, la, la, la!
-Does he come here every day?
-Today's a holiday. Kindergarten's closed.
I have to take him out to burn off energy
or he won't sleep at night.
Get him an iPad. It's easier.
An iPad will make him near-sighted.
How about you stop that?
I'll take you to buy an ice cream.
Ice cream has trans fats.
You shouldn't eat it.
Hey. Looks like Gerald
does have a crypto account.
PRIVATE KEY
PRIVATE KEY, UNLOCK WALLET
GERALD CHEN, $3,246,161.82 (UDST)
100 million in Taiwan dollars.
100 million? Holy shit.
He left you that much?
Gerald wouldn't just have left money.
He would have left other clues.
I just traced
Gerald's cryptocurrency account.
There was a large transfer
just before he disappeared.
He bought a house in the mountains.
I'll send the address when I find it.
So he bought a house.
Could he be hiding out there?
I'll come with you tomorrow.
I never said I'd go.
It's possible he might not want you
to get involved.
Gerald and Ben have always been
very protective of me.
But they haven't taken care of themselves.
You think he's out there.
Am I right?
We'll know when we see him.
Hey, eat something.
It's getting cold.
What's with the radish and pork?
I have to eat too.
Why would anyone want to eat that?
You want some? Fried tofu.
The skin's gross. No.
You're a child. Try some.
If I have to.
-Mmm.
-That was radish you ate!
-Tofu.
-Show me then.
-Bah.
-Uh!
-Uh.
-I didn't see it.
-Swallowed it.
-You have to eat another one.
-I just ate it.
You obviously ate a radish.
Then eat a blood pudding.
-If you eat a pork meatball.
-Eat this. Here.
Mm. Mm.
Eat some pork.
I'm gonna eat one, all right?
That was obviously tofu.
Hey. Why do you think
Gerald left so much money for Mina?
What's going on there?
AUTHENTIC TIEN-BU-LA
Mina.
-Back then when she stumbled on us…
-Yeah.
…I was going to kill her.
It was Gerald saved her life.
Oh.
And then she hung around you guys.
Does she have any family?
-She was a runaway.
-Yeah?
I'd never seen a child that young
who could be so--
-Difficult.
-Stubborn.
-Think so?
-I know so.
-Ah.
-She's not afraid of anything.
It's as if all the worst things
have already happened to her.
So this is why she's how she is.
Ah.
Now I get it. Ah. Very believable.
But after meeting you guys,
she… she's a lot more talkative.
-Really?
-Mm.
Hey.
Do you think Gerald's still with us?
In our line of work,
you don't get to do it till you retire.
If I hadn't lost this leg,
I wouldn't have made it this far.
What happened to your leg?
Ah.
Failed mission.
Yeh Yueh Tong decided I was useless,
so they let me retire with honor.
That's inhuman.
-Fucking hell.
-Mm.
Hey, listen.
-When I retire, I wanna have a stall.
-Hm.
Specifically swamp eel.
I'll set up next to you.
We'd be a one-stop shop. How about it?
Leave me out of it. It'd be crowded.
You wanna do that? Go way over there.
Wouldn't it be nice to have company?
I'm worried you'll be cold and lonely
in your old age.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ho.
You don't get it. You…
-Drink your soup.
-I'm good.
-Deep-fried tofu?
-No, really.
-I'm home.
-Are you now?
-You haven't gone to bed yet.
-No.
Uh, where's Howie?
-Doing homework in his room.
-Ah. I got you a snack.
Tien-bu-la with blood pudding.
-Oh.
-Hm.
Howie! Your father brought
a midnight snack.
Come and eat.
-Hey, hold on.
-Yeah?
What's in the bag?
Ah. Young Gold thought I needed
new clothes, so he bought me these.
-Ah, your boss treats you so well.
-Mm.
Handsome and generous.
Invite him over for dinner
when he gets time.
-Great. Will do, will do.
-Good.
What do you call this?
Why are you shutting your door?
I was about to take a shower.
You're so sneaky.
-Out of the way.
-I know you're up to something.
Seriously.
Oh!
You're in a good mood.
I was thinking about
what your dad got for my last birthday.
-Was that the fill light?
-That's right.
And the message was something like,
"Wendy Wu, beautiful as a fairy,
thanks to this light."
-It sucked.
-He always gets it wrong.
I have to say, your father,
he's got it right this time.
Madame Fan.
They found Gerald.
Make sure they're not alerted.
Get fixers to keep watch.
Anything happens, report back.
Okay.
While he's still alive,
we won't be able to face our client.
You know what to do.
I want it clean.
Yeh Yueh Tong can't be implicated.
No problem.
-Yeah?
-I have some things to do at home.
I won't be coming over
to third wheel today.
You're a slacker.
This cool autumn weather
is perfect for an outing.
Take advantage of the opportunity, okay?
-Bye-bye.
-Hey!
When you're in the States,
if you need money, just tell me.
I hear that things
are super expensive there.
Don't suffer. There's no need to be proud.
Don't worry.
You've already given me enough.
And I've applied for a job there.
So I can pay you back later.
It's just what I owed your father before.
Felix.
Listen to me.
You've been taking care of me
all these years.
When mom was sick, you helped out.
It's my turn.
Ah, you shouldn't be worrying about money.
Focus on study.
Hey, I'll take you to the airport
in the morning.
It's all right.
I've already booked a ride.
-Hey.
-Yeah?
This is for you on behalf of your dad.
Your dad's greatest wish
was to send you abroad to study.
And for you to see the world.
Now I've helped him fulfil it.
Help me out.
Oh. Here we are.
From now on,
when you're wearing this,
It'll be like…
It'll be like
your dad's right next to you.
Okay, done.
I'll come back to visit you.
Look after yourself.
Ah. Don't cry.
When you cry, you're uglier than your dad.
Why do you always have to do that?
-You're so annoying.
-I'm gonna go pee.
Huh?
You're so weird.
Why are you stepping down so suddenly?
Is there someone you'd like to nominate?
I've gotten too old for this.
It's time I stepped down.
While the step's still there,
stepping down's very easy.
If you wait till the step's taken away,
no matter how you do it,
you're gonna get hurt.
Terra,
this is a heavy step.
It will take a lot of people to move it.
There are a lot of people
who wanna move it.
Like father, like daughter.
And this outsider has a lot of support.
They outnumber the insider support.
I'm old. I can't get involved anymore.
Old friend,
I hope you get to leave on a high note.
I'll have the tea waiting.
THE TIMES ARE AGAINST ME. WHAT CAN I DO?
Excuse me.
Can you please
interpret this fortune stick for me?
"Your path to fame is not yet clear,
with stormy clashes drawing near."
"Guard both sides from pain and loss."
"Relax, sigh not
and wait your toss." There.
Are you asking
for family, luck, or career?
Madam Fan got it for you.
Yes?
We go up this path and we're there.
LIEN HSIN BRIDGE
He's probably after the same thing.
It's Yeh Yueh Tong's fixer.
Madam Fan knows they've found Gerald.
Come on.
Excuse me.
Have you seen this person?
Thank you.
All branches have been notified
of the time of the secret meeting.
Mm.
The gods have spoken.
I drew Lot 28.
"The golden days of old have nearly gone."
"A mighty tiger now stranded and drawn."
"Fortune is fickle, fey, and fleet."
"So seize the hour before it flees."
You recall the stories behind this slip?
One was Cao Cao's capture
after meeting Zhang Xiu in Wancheng.
The other was Xiang Yu,
who, defeated and surrounded by enemies
at Wu River, decided to end it.
Mm. One was betrayed,
yet was able to escape danger
and achieve dominance.
The other, a hero who lost faith.
He'd reached the end of the line.
Hey.
Which one,
in your opinion,
Is the slip about?
This depends on whether
the individual concerned
can adapt
and humble themselves to survive.
You're right.
Am I needed for anything else?
No. Thank you.
You've been working so hard
for Ching He lately.
Take a few days off. Get some rest.
You let Gold go along to find Gerald.
If he learns the truth, don't you fear
what the consequences will be?
If it's something he needed to know,
someone would have told him soon enough.
I fear this decision was made in haste.
Once some things are known,
there is no going back.
Hm.
The garden looks cared for.
There's someone around.
Zoe?
Hey.
What do you want?
Stay there.
Just put the gun down.
Don't hurt your child.
Stay there.
Why?
Why won't you leave me alone?
We won't hurt you.
We're here for Gerald Chen.
He went AWOL a year ago
and left us a clue to find him here.
You're the one in the photo.
You and Gerald.
What was your relationship?
He was the one who came to kill me.
Are you here yet?
I'm not coming.
Don't contact me again.
Wait. William!
Hello?
When he saw that I was pregnant.
He couldn't go through with it.
If Gerald didn't finish the job,
Yeh Yueh Tong wouldn't spare him,
and you wouldn't still be here.
That's why we faked my death.
We fooled everyone.
Target Zoe
confirmed dead.
Why are you helping me?
I don't wanna fuck up again.
Then he brought me here to lie low.
So, where's he?
GERALD CHEN
Yes?
I might not be able to get there again.
There's a bag of cash in the ceiling.
Enough for you and your daughter.
Once things calm down--
Wait.
You there?
That was the last time he called.
He could be dead.
He's not.
He would have planned everything.
He probably knew his life was in danger
when he was sent to kill me.
What do you mean?
Before accepting the mission,
Gerald must have known
that Yeh Yueh Tong would eliminate him
to protect this secret.
Why does Yeh Yueh Tong wanna kill you?
What's so important
so many people need to die?
Your family.
What do you mean?
The Hsueh clan.
They killed my husband.
And would have killed me and my daughter.
We were fortunate.
I'd happily take all of you with me.
-Why does the Hsueh clan--
-Don't come any closer!
Anyway, a life for a life.
That's some justice.
Just calm down.
Why did my family
kill William and your husband?
What's it all for?
Do you honestly have no idea?
The Hsin Nan redevelopment zone
is so huge.
It was approved so quickly. That wouldn't
have happened without your family.
William helped them launder the money.
You must have known that.
I just want us to be safe.
Pretend that I'm dead. I'm not gonna talk.
Don't worry.
We won't tell anyone.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Wendy
Yay! Blow out the candles.
Yay!
Mom, here you are.
Oh, you're such a good son. Thank you.
Hey, your husband's
pretty amazing as well.
Thank you.
MOM
Perfume?
Oh yeah. Hey, do you remember
when you were pregnant with Howie?
We were at the shopping center,
and you smelled this scent
and you really wanted it,
and you couldn't
bring yourself to buy it, hm?
-Felix.
-Hm?
A husband and wife
can tell each other anything, right?
Mm.
Are you hiding something?
What would I be hiding?
Ah, you're imagining things.
Go to sleep, will you, okay?
Are you sure?
Yes, really.
You are so weird.
The kid hasn't spilled, has he?
What did you say?
Oh, it was nothing,
Nothing. Go to sleep
and don't dream, will you?
Off to sleep now.
From the exam results,
it looks like
Mr. Hsueh's liver cancer has metastasized.
He should begin treatment
as soon as possible.
Okay, I understand.
Doctor, this news must be kept secret.
All right.
My illness might be of benefit to you.
Look. Pick the right time
to announce it to the public.
The timing is critical.
There can be no errors. You got that?
Mm.
And also,
you can't tell your brother yet.
Okay.
Dad,
get some rest.
The situation's changed.
I always thought
that if we kept searching…
then he was still with us.
He left you the necklace.
Perhaps he hoped, one day,
that you'd meet up at that house.
He knew he was going to die.
That's why he left the necklace for me
before carrying out the mission.
But he never expected you
to join Yeh Yueh Tong.
What are you going to do?
Madam Fan's kept me close all this time
just so she can track down Gerald.
What is it?
The fact Zoe's alive
isn't just bad for Yeh Yueh Tong.
It's also a threat
to the Hsueh clan.
I won't hurt her.
I know you won't do that.
At least not at the moment.
Meaning?
I can't predict
what you could do just to score points.
From the very beginning,
I was used by you to find her.
Isn't that right?
Ching He
is holding a secret meeting today.
The six leaders will be there.
No doubt there'll be fireworks.
TERRA
Terra has always been on time.
What's going on today?
EARTH
Oh, what a pity.
There'll be an apology.
Everyone…
Chairman,
Terra won't be coming.
Terra was found dead in the suburbs.
How could this happen?
We should adjourn.
We will resume
after I've investigated Terra's death.
Chairman,
we should take our time discussing
If there are better candidates
for the position of Fixer Celestial.
What do you mean by that?
The Hong family, for generations,
have served Ching He well.
Everything we do
is in Ching He's best interests.
Ching He has stood strong for 100 years
because of leaders who know
how to adapt to changing circumstances
and make the best choice.
Sir Hong's already agreed to hand over
the key to Kuang Ming Chamber.
But the chair,
he won't step down so easily.
After such a serious incident,
as chair,
I have to investigate thoroughly.
I have a way to deal with Thackery.
Oh, do tell.
You'll find out.
Madam Fan,
here's to us.
LULLABY
This is a life-saving charm.
If you find yourself in danger,
use this to call Ching He.
Hello?
Gerald Chen told me
that if my life was in danger,
I should call this number.